DMITRY STARKOV

Moscow, Russia



starkdev@icloud.com



linkedin.com/in/starkdev

Summary

I'm 24 years old. Graduated from professional college. Studied at CVUT in Prague. Travelling through Europe. Living in Prague and Moscow. Fast learning programmer for more than 9 years. Last 4 years I'm working on Mobile Development. Registered in Apple and Google developer programs.

All languages, skills and technologies mentioned below not only studied, but also applied in practice. By default my applications are covered by Unit and UI Tests, has CI/CD integration based on Github Actions and Fastlane, uses Git as version control system. I always interested in learning new languages and technologies like TensorFlow, AR or GraphQL and applying it in mobile or desktop applications I working on.

Programming languages with professional knowledge:

- Swift (4+ years)
- Python (2+ years)
- Dart (1+ years)
- C (2 years)
- C++ (2 years)
- C# (2+ years)
- Javascript (1 year)
- NodeJS (1 year)
- Visual Basic (1 year)
- Delphi (1 year)
- Bash (6 month)

Skills and Knowledges: iOS Applications, Desktop Applications, Crossplatform Applications, Web Services, Progressive Web Applications, Chat Bots, Workflow Automation, Data Mining, Web Scraping, Application Security, In-App Purchases, Advertising, Analytics, Machine Learning, NLP, Cryptography, SQL, GraphQL, NoSQL, Network Interception, MITM, Data Mockup, Automate Testing, Automate Screenshots, CI/CD, Lottie Animations, Json Web Tokens, Realm, Core Data, Combine, Alamofire, SwiftLint, SwiftPM, CocoaPods, SwiftUI, UIKit, WPF, XAML, HTML, JSON, XML, CSV, Regex, Dio, Hive, GetX, Provider.

Technologies and Tools: Xcode, Flutter, VS Code, Visual Studio, Git, Github Actions, Fastlane, Firebase, Parse Server, Cisco, Microsoft SQL Server, Oracle Database, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, TensorFlow, Blockchain, Wolfram Mathematica, Google App Engine, Google AdMob, .Net, Selenium, Postman.

Communication: Conversational English (B1), Native Russian (C2) and Fluent Czech (B2).

Experience



Mobile Application Developer

Self-employed

Feb 2018 - Present (3 years 4 months +)

Developing Mobile Applications for App Store and Google Play.

iOS Applications using Swift and SwiftUI. Cross-platform Applications using Flutter.

Python Developer

Self-employed

Aug 2016 - Jan 2018 (1 year 6 months)

Server-Side Applications, Chat Bots, Automate Cryptocurrency Trading, Machine Learning Models, NLP and Computer Vision using Python Language.

Education



Representation Technology CTU in Prague

2018 - 2019



Programming College

2012 - 2016

Skills

Research • User Experience (UX) • Continuous Integration • Project Planning • Testing • iOS Development • Machine Learning • Flutter • GraphQL • Teamwork